<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Apple Hot News</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/hotnews/</link>
<description>Hot News provided by Apple.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2009, Apple Inc.</copyright>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 08:39:56 PST</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 08:39:56 PST</lastBuildDate>
<category>Apple</category>
<generator>In house</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss/</docs><item>
<title>Take the new FileMaker 10 UI Tour</title>
<link>http://www.filemaker.com/products/fmp/features.html?sr=hotnews</link>
<description>To illustrate many of the new features introduced in FileMaker 10, FileMaker now offers a series of Quick Tours on its website. The tours take us through the new interface (particularly the new Status Toolbar), show us some of the new database Themes and Templates, and demonstrate Script Triggers, Save Finds, Dynamic Reports, and other features new to FileMaker 10. 

</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2009 08:39:05 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>App Store Pick of the Week: iPump Pilates</title>
<link>http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewSoftware?id=292835472&amp;mt=8&amp;sr=hotnews</link>
<description>Resolved to get — and stay — in shape this year? Then you may want to try out iPump Pilates. The app guides and inspires you through a strength training and body toning fitness regimen and makes it easy to log and track your progress. Developed by fitness pros, iPump Pilates is one of 20 fitness apps from iPump on the App Store. 

</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 08:51:47 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Now on iTunes: It’s Oprah</title>
<link>http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewArtist?id=280669922</link>
<description>With such video and audio podcasts as Oprah.com’s Health and Wellness Channel, Oprah.com’s Spirt Channel, and Oprah.com’s Money Channel, you can now enjoy some of your favorite Oprah programming whenever you’d like.  Download and watch individual podcasts. Or subscribe to a channel and have iTunes automatically download each new episode for you. Enjoy.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2009 09:08:01 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iPhoto ’09 wins Best of Show award at Macworld</title>
<link>http://www.macworld.com/article/138002-2/2009/01/bos2009.html?sr=hotnews</link>
<description>“iPhoto ‘09 looks like reason enough to upgrade to the latest version of iLife,” say the Macworld editors who distinguished iPhoto ’09 as a Best of Show award winner at Macworld Expo 2009. Macworld editors praise the addition of Faces (which introduces “face-detection and facial-recognition technology” to iPhoto) and Places (which lets photographers organize photos by location). 
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 13:01:42 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Quick Tip of the Week: BCC in Mail</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/business/theater/#tutorial=bccinmail?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>In addition to the To, CC, and Subject fields, Mail in Mac OS X Leopard lets you easily add a BCC field to a new Mail message, so that you can blind carbon copy one or more recipients. See how easily you can add a BCC field to your next email message by watching the latest Quick Tip of the Week.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2009 11:22:50 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Learn how to use Spaces in the Science Productivity Lab</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/science/productivitylab/#tutorial=organizingspaces&amp;?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>If you’re not using Spaces in Mac OS X Leopard, you’re missing out on a highly useful productivity tool. That’s because Spaces helps you banish the clutter from your display by grouping similar applications — Mail, iChat, and Safari, for example — in a single space. With Spaces, you can even run Windows applications in one space and effortlessly switch to your Mac applications using a single keystroke.. 

</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 10:13:56 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>If you dig dinosaurs…</title>
<link>http://deimos3.apple.com/WebObjects/Core.woa/Browse/naturalsciences.org.1750424131?sr=hotnews</link>
<description>You’ll enjoy “Fossil Fields.” Brought to us by the North Carolina Museum of Natural Sciences, the iTune U video podcasts introduce us to the rich coastal fossil fields found in North Carolina and other areas in the southeastern US. These fossils reveal that wooly and prairie mammoths, walruses, giant sloths, whales, and numerous invertebrate species inhabited the region up to 220 million years ago.

</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 09:44:33 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Coming Attractions: Hotel for Dogs</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/trailers/paramount/hotelfordogs/?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>When Andi (Emma Roberts) and her younger brother Bruce (Jake T. Austin) need to find a new home for their dog Friday, fate drags them to an abandoned hotel that the pair (and their friends) transform into a  Hotel for Dogs. If the trailers are any indication, the film offers lots of tail-wagging fun. Opening in theaters on January 16, it also stars Kyla Pratt, Lisa Kudrow, and Kevin Dillon.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 09:39:27 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Take iWork ’09 out for a spin</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/iwork/download-trial/?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>With all of the new features just added to iWork ’09, now’s a great time to take Apple’s great productivity suite out for a test drive. Just visit our website to download the free, 30-day trial version of iWork ’09. And as you experiment with Pages, Numbers, and Keynote on your Mac, be sure to watch the tutorials and learn more about all three applications. </description>
<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 08:52:58 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>App Store Pick of the Week: Keynote Remote</title>
<link>http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewSoftware?id=300719251&amp;mt=8?sr=hotnews</link>
<description>Now you can maintain complete control of your Keynote presentation using your iPhone or iPod touch. Thanks to Keynote Remote ($0.99). The new App Store application works with Keynote ’09 (part of the new iWork ’09 productivity suite), letting you progress through your slides with a swipe. Hold iPhone vertically, and you see presenter notes; horizontally, and you see the current and next slide in your presentation.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2009 09:03:24 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Changes come to the iTunes Store</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/itunes/whatsnew/?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Beginning today, all four major music labels — Universal Music Group, Sony BMG, Warner Music Group and EMI — and thousands of independent labels, now offer their music in the DRM-free iTunes Plus format with higher-quality 256 kbps AAC encoding. iTunes customers can also now purchase and download songs directly onto their iPhone 3G over their 3G network — just as they do with Wi-Fi today — for the same price as downloading to their computer. And in April, based on what the music labels charge Apple, songs on iTunes will be available for 69¢, 99¢, or $1.29, with most albums still priced at $9.99.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 08:46:51 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple introduces new 17-inch MacBook Pro</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/macbookpro/?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>The new 17-inch MacBook Pro features a durable and beautiful aluminum unibody enclosure and a revolutionary new built-in battery delivering up to 8 hours of use and up to 1,000 recharges. It has a high resolution LED-backlit display and the same large glass Multi-Touch trackpad introduced with the new MacBook family. The new notebook also includes state-of-the-art NVIDIA graphics and the latest generation Intel Core 2 Duo mobile processors, available up to 2.93 GHz. </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 08:32:49 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Introducing iLife ’09</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ilife/?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today unveiled iLife ’09, which includes major upgrades to iPhoto, iMovie, and GarageBand and an updated version of iWeb. iPhoto ’09 introduces Faces and Places, breakthrough ways to easily organize and manage photos based on who appears in them and where they were taken. In iMovie ’09, you’ll find powerful, yet easy-to-use new features that let you create a movie quickly or add refinements and special effects if you have more time. And GarageBand ’09 now offers a fun new way to learn to play piano and guitar with Basic Lessons, which teach fundamentals, and Artist Lessons (sold separately), in which original artists teach you how to play the songs they made famous.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 08:21:14 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple unveils iWork ’09</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/iwork/?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Available today, iWork ’09 adds powerful new features to each of its popular productivity applications. Keynote ’09 introduces Magic Move, which offers an easy way to automatically animate any image, graphic or text repeated on consecutive slides. In Pages ’09, a new Full Screen view lets you focus solely on your writing while the new outline mode lets you organize your thoughts. And Numbers ’09 introduces a quick way to group and summarize data and a dramatically simplified way to create complex formulas. Apple also introduced the public beta of iWork.com, a new service for sharing documents online.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2009 08:10:51 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Now Available: FileMaker Pro 10</title>
<link>http://www.filemaker.com/products/fmp/index.html?sr=hotnews</link>
<description>FileMaker today announced the availability of FileMaker Pro 10. The new version of its award-winning software features a sleek new interface and intuitive new design. For example, database users can now place frequently used FileMaker features in the redesigned and customizable Status Toolbar, resulting in streamlined navigation, better workflow, and time-saving shortcuts.
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 11:55:23 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Quick Tip of the Week: Selecting multiple email messages</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/business/theater/#tutorial=selectmailmessages?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Ever receive multiple, related email messages that you’d like to file in the same folder or delete? You could delete or drag them into a folder one message at a time. But in Mail, you can save time by deleting  or filing all the messages at once. Find out how by watching the latest Quick Tip of the Week. </description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 11:02:46 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>App Store pioneering “a new kind of business” </title>
<link>http://www.nytimes.com/2009/01/02/technology/personaltech/02apps.html?_r=1&amp;ref=technology&amp;?sr=hotnews</link>
<description>“The new status symbol,” report Matt Richtel and Laura M. Holson (nytimes.com) “is what your phone can do — count calories, teach Spanish, simulate a flute, or fling a monkey from a tree.”  While some “programs can genuinely help productivity,” others are simply “jaw-dropping“ fun. The apps, say the authors, “have become a form of social currency” that is driving “a new kind of business.”</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 08:33:27 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Smashing Research at CERN</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/science/profiles/briancox/?sr=hotnews?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>“The 17-inch MacBook Pro is my main computer,” says Brian Cox. A particle physicist, Cox works at the CERN Large Hadron Collider, which scientists will soon use to try to recreate the “Big Bang.” Cox uses the Mac because it can run both UNIX for research and productivity apps for everything else. And he’s not alone. “When you look around a physics conference now,” he says, “you see more Macs than anything else.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 16:13:27 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>App Store Pick of the Week: The Weather Channel</title>
<link>http://itunes.apple.com/WebObjects/MZStore.woa/wa/viewSoftware?id=295646461&amp;mt=8?sr=hotnews</link>
<description>If you’re traveling this holiday season, be sure to take the Weather Channel with you. Yes, everyone’s favorite source for weather now takes to the road on iPhone and iPod touch. The Weather Channel app offers location-based weather, customizable weather maps, and severe weather alerts. You can even share a weather alert or forecast by emailing it from your iPhone or iPod touch. 

</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 09:22:56 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Interested in Science?</title>
<link>http://deimos3.apple.com/WebObjects/Core.woa/Browse/wgbh.org.1387053431?sr=hotnews</link>
<description>Then you’ll enjoy the Forum Network Lectures brought to us by WGBH. In the mostly video lectures, we hear noted  planetologists, mathematical physicists, authors, and biologists explore such subjects as the birth and death of stars, the canopy ecosystem of coastal redwoods, and time travel. Come and “entertain your brain” with the Cambridge Forum Network Lectures on iTunes U.

</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2008 09:09:17 PST</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>